https://emergeortho.com/privacy-policy/

Physician's Referral
DoctorsProvider TypeDoctorsPhysician Assistants & Nurse PractitionersPhysical & Occupational Therapists & AssistantsAthletic TrainersPsychologistsBy RegionBlue Ridge RegionFoothills RegionTriad RegionTriangle RegionWilmington Region CloseSpecialties & ServicesOrthopedic SpecialtiesAccessOrtho Orthopedic Urgent CareBack, Neck & SpineElbow & ArmExceptional Foot and Ankle Pain SpecialistsFoot & AnkleGeneral OrthopedicsHand & WristHip & KneeJoint ReplacementPediatric OrthopedicsPodiatryShoulderSports MedicineSports-Related ConcussionTraumaNon-Orthopedic SpecialtiesAnesthesiologyBone HealthBreast CareGeneral SurgeryInterventional Pain ManagementNeurologyPhysical Medicine and Rehabilitation and PhysiatryRheumatologyVein ClinicWound Care CenterServicesBlood Flow Restriction TherapyBody CompositionBundled Payment ProgramDiagnosticsPhysical & Occupational TherapyTelemedicineWorkers’ Compensation CloseFor PatientsPatient EducationMedical Forms for PatientsInsuranceBilling & Payment OptionsClinical Trials & Research CloseLocationsLocations MapBlue Ridge RegionFoothills RegionTriad RegionTriangle RegionWilmington Region CloseAbout UsAbout EmergeOrthoContactNewsCareers Close
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
We do not collect information from visitors of our site or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
How do we protect your information?
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
We do collect credit card information, but did not know PCI compliant scans are now required.
We do not use Malware Scanning.
We do not use an SSL certificate
We do not need an SSL because we have no information to protect.
Do we use ‘cookies’?
We do not use cookies for tracking purposes
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.
However, you will still be able to place orders .
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.
Third-party links
We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.
Google
Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
• Demographics and Interests Reporting
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out: Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify the users via in-site notification
• Within 7 business days
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
Attn: Privacy Officer
EmergeOrtho, P.A.
120 William Penn Plaza
Durham, NC 27704
HIPAA@emergeortho.com
Join the EmergeOrtho E-Mail List
Stay informed about the latest orthopedic specialties, news, and upcoming events.
Enroll Today
Blue RidgeRegion
828.258.8800
FoothillsRegion
866.324.2850
TriadRegion
336.545.5000
TriangleRegion
800.359.3053
WilmingtonRegion
910.332.3800
DoctorsSpecialties & ServicesFor PatientsLocationsAbout UsNews
ContactPay OnlinePatient PortalPhysician’s Referral FormsNotice of Privacy Practices
The contents of the emergeortho.com site, such as text, graphics, images, and other material contained on the emergeortho.com site (“content”) are for informational purposes only. The content is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health providers with any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on the emergeortho.com site.
© 2020 EmergeOrtho. All Rights Reserved.
Design by Farotech
Privacy PolicyNon-Discrimination NoticeLimited English Proficiency
Request An Appointment
Urgent Care
Find A Doctor
Patient Portal
Request An Appointment
Please enter your information below and our office will be in touch with you.
Urgent Care
Enter your zip code below to find the nearest place of care.
By RegionBlue Ridge RegionFoothills RegionTriad RegionTriangle RegionWilmington Region
Filter Locations
Find A Doctor
Select one of the filters below to find a doctor.
By RegionBlue Ridge RegionFoothills RegionTriad RegionTriangle RegionWilmington Region
By Specialty & ServicesAccessOrtho Orthopedic Urgent CareAnesthesiologyBack, Neck & SpineBlood Flow Restriction TherapyBody CompositionBone HealthBreast CareBundled Payment ProgramDiagnosticsElbow & ArmExceptional Foot and Ankle Pain SpecialistsFoot & AnkleGeneral OrthopedicsGeneral SurgeryHand & WristHip & KneeInterventional Pain ManagementJoint ReplacementMAKOplasty®NeurologyPediatric OrthopedicsPhysical & Occupational TherapyPhysical Medicine and Rehabilitation and PhysiatryPodiatryRheumatologyShoulderSports MedicineSports-Related ConcussionTelemedicineTraumaVein ClinicWorkers' CompensationWound Care Center
Filter
Join the EmergeOrtho E-Mail List
Stay informed about the latest orthopedic specialties, news, and upcoming events.
